Kelly is a very strong-willed person.
And if she didn't want to do something,
she didn't do it.
And one day I picked her up from school.
She was just arguing with me.
And she just kept on going and going.
And then I said,
you know how to push my buttons, don't you?
And she said,
mom, you show me a button and I'll push it.
And then I said,
I'll pull over and you're going to get out of my car.
And she said, I can't do that.
And I said, why?
And she said,
because you have to take me home.
And I said, I'll put, I'm going to let you get out and you can walk home.
And she said,
and if you do that, I'm going to call the police.
So, anyways, that's how it ended.
I ended up leaving her in the car and taking her home.
But she always argued with me about everything.
When we would go to the coast
and we would walk along the cliffs,
I would have to put like a leash on her
because she was so stubborn and she wouldn't want to go by herself,
but she would just take off and go.
So I always had to keep her in.
So everybody said I was mean because I put a leash on her.
I think we started going camping with Kelly when she was one.
She was still in diapers
and we took her everywhere
and we'd go for two weeks at a time.
And we have a backpack that we would put her in.
And so we were, went hiking all the time
and on binky bottle patrol. whoever was behind her.
So because she always had her binky and her bottle with her.
So if she would lose it, oh, and her blankie. So somebody would always have to rescue them.
Well, I remember Christmas.
I remember one of her Christmas that the neighbor was dressed up as Santa Claus.
And when she went to bed, we had him come over.
And  kissed her on the cheek in bed,
and then we took pictures of Santa Claus putting presents under the tree for her.
So then when she was really excited,
of course she put out the milk and the cookies for him, and they were gone.
So she was happy that Santa came.
So, yeah.
I think it was hard. I know when she was going off to college.
Having her be gone like that for the first time.
And then she didn't come home.
She went on to Europe for a while after college,
and then she met you.
This interview ends by, you're here, you brought my daughter back home,
and now I have two wonderful grandchildren and a wonderful son in law.
So, it makes me happy.